pciservices.com 2014-12-07

# pciservices.com - privacy policy | PCI services

Privacy Policy Request Info Tell a Friend PrintThe following section describes PCI's privacy practices, including its policy for information received about you during visits to the Web Site:

The amount and type of information received depends on how you use the Web Site. Your User ID and Password may be temporarily stored in a cookie allowing us to free resources for other customers if you are logged on but not actively using the portal. Data stored in the cookie will allow you to automatically log back on without re-entering your information during the same session.

PCI will only use this information to identify and access your account to provide the requested services. Cookies and all data stored in the cookie will expire once you log off the PCI system.

If you access or use the Web Site without using one of our online services, we do not collect or store information that will identify you. However, we may collect and store other information such as the name of your Internet Service Provider, the referral Web Site, requested pages including date and time of requests and other information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of customer visits. In addition, we may request information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number or social security number to provide you with a service or correspondence (such as promotional material) or to respond to questions or comments you send us. Such information (including your type of request and other information) is collected, stored and used in accordance with applicable laws and in a manner appropriate to the nature of your request and is used to fulfill it.  
Information you provide to PCI is also used to improve the services we provide to you.

We may share personal information with our affiliates, other companies or agents in order for them to provide services for us; such information is shared and protected in accordance with applicable law. We do not otherwise share with or sell personal information to unrelated companies.  As we continue to develop our business, we may buy or sell business divisions or companies, we may merge or combine with another company, or our company itself, or all or a significant part of its assets, may be acquired by another company. In such transactions, this information generally is one of the transferred and shared business assets. The information transferred and shared remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy notice (unless, of course, you have agreed to be subject to new privacy notice terms). We may decide to release your personal information if we believe release is appropriate or necessary to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Web Site terms of use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of pciservices.com, our users, or others. This information may be released or exchanged with other companies and organizations to protect against fraud or illegal activity, or for credit risk reduction. We will cooperate with law enforcement and judicial and regulatory authorities, and we may provide personally identifiable information to appropriate government authorities upon receipt of a subpoena or court order, or to cooperate with a law enforcement or regulatory investigation. We will fully cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement and regulatory agencies activities that we in good faith believe to be illegal. We undertake no obligation or duty to release such information, however, unless we are required to do so under applicable laws.

We provide email links on our "Contact Us" page that allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We may receive a confirmation when you open any e-mail that we send to you, if your computer supports such capabilities. If you send us any email, we will retain such email and your email address for response. We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary or duplicate messages to you.

This Web Site is not directed or marketed at, nor intended for, children under 13 years of age.  PCI does not knowingly collect any information, including personally identifiable information, from children under 13 years of age.  If we learn that any information was provided to it through this Web Site by a person younger than 13 years of age, we will delete the information immediately.

PCI may modify this privacy policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. If PCI changes its privacy policy, the revised policy will apply only after the effective date of the revised policy. Your continued use of this Web Site following any new policy that is posted will be deemed your conclusive acceptance of the modified policy so you should periodically review this policy to be aware of such modifications.

Our online privacy policy applies only to information that we collect from customers online who visit www.pciservices.com, and any other affiliated website that refers to this privacy policy.  It does not apply to any information collected at our distribution centers or other physical locations. This Web Site contains links to other websites.   You should review the privacy statements of any sites operated by other companies or organizations that are linked to this Web Site in order to understand how that site collects, uses and shares your personal information. PCI is not responsible for the privacy statements or practices of sites and services controlled by other companies or organizations.

If you choose to visit our Web Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this privacy notice and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.  References above to “applicable law” mean the law of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania and US federal law.  

If you have any concerns or questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web Site, please Contact Us (at the link above) and we will endeavor to resolve the problem.

© Packaging Coordinators Inc 2013
